# H.R. Johnson

Community-Driven in Kalamazoo, Michigan find.serendipity@gmail.com & linkedin.com/in/findserendipity 360-951-0354

#### Summary

Experienced professional with 15+ years in customer service and community management. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a commitment to excellence and attention to detail. Adherent to high standards while working to understand, meet, and exceed client expectations.

#### Skills

Languages | French (Intermediate), JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, LaTeX, PHP

Tools and Technologies | HTML, CSS, React.js, REST, Git, Express.js, Node.js, Next.js, Jira, HubSpot CRM, Apps Scripts, Miro, Figma, Canva, Hootsuite, Zendesk, Microsoft Suite, GitHub, VS Code, WSL, Docker, Linux, Kanban, Agile, A/B Testing, Facebook, Instagram, X/Twitter, Discord, Telegram, Reddit, LinkedIn

 $\textbf{Proficiencies} \parallel \text{Customer Service, Sales, Community Management, Social Media Management, Customer Support, Event Management, Crisis Management}$ 

#### Experience

## Air Zoo Aviation Museum, Kalamazoo, MI | Guest Experience Ambassador Aug 24 - Current

- Handled cash, inventory, and front desk duties including adding customers to member database.
- Guided guests through museum experience while operating from a stationary assignment.
- Engaged guests in a fast-paced environment, providing detailed answers about planes, artifacts, and the museum.
- Helped manage flow of crowds, efficiently helping guests with needs and directing as needed.
- Ensured guest safety in various situations with various crowd sizes.

#### Communitrix, Remote | Founder

Sep 2023 - Current

- $\bullet\,$  Obtained and maintained a small but strong client base.
- Drafted and implemented community management plans for clients, including social strategies for Facebook and Reddit.
- Maintained specific client codebases, updating sites to maintain modern security protocols.
- Created standard and milestone-based contracts for all work started with clients.

#### Community.co, Remote | Community Manager

July 2019 - June 2023

- Upsold events and memberships to members via forums and email marketing campaigns
- Managed communities for various high-profile clients, increasing community engagement from 2% to 7%
- Designed and developed Google Apps Scripts for engagement and retention projects
- Trained team members in data collection, analysis, and reporting

# Internet Brands, Remote $\parallel$ Community Manager

 $July\ 2013-July\ 2019$ 

- Created incentives for members to purchase larger or longer memberships
- Managed cross-functional teams in community forums and customer support
- $\bullet$  Increased customer satisfaction from 61% to 96% through strategic initiatives
- Handled customer support issues and abuse reports

### Education

#### Fullstack Academy, Remote | Junior Developer

Feb 2024 - June 2024

# University of Washington, Seattle | Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology

2011

• Top-ranking graduate, Summa cum laude